spreety.com 2012-12-01

# About Spreety TV Online Copyright / Privacy Policy

### Spreety Copyright / Privacy Policy

**Usage of Materials with Copyrights**

The usage of materials covered by copyrights is considered legal under fair use. Only portions of the content is displayed, and for images, at a lower resolution, with the intent for promotion. 

Spreety will review all claims of copyright infringement received and remove content deemed to have been posted or distributed in violation of any such laws. To make a claim, please provide us with the following: 

  * A physical or electronic signature of the copyright owner or the person authorized to act on its behalf.
  * A description of the copyrighted work claimed to have been infringed.
  * A description of the infringing material and information reasonably sufficient to permit Spreety to locate the material.
  * Your contact information, including your name, address, telephone number, and email.
  * A statement by you that you have a good faith belief that use of the material in the manner complained of is not authorized by the copyright owner, its agent, or the law.
  * A statement that the information in the notification is accurate, and, under the pains and penalties of perjury, that you are authorized to act on behalf of the copyright owner.

**Privacy/Security Statement**

Spreety is committed to maintaining the privacy of your personal information and the security of our computer systems. With respect to the collection, use, and disclosure of personal information, Spreety makes every effort to ensure compliance with applicable Federal law. 

As a general rule, Spreety does not collect personally-identifying information about you when you visit our site, unless you choose to provide such information to us. The information we receive depends upon what you do when visiting our site. 

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit networkadvertising.org. 

_If you visit our site to read or download information, we may collect and store the following information:_

  * The name of the domain from which you access the Internet. 
  * The Internet address of the website from which you linked directly to our site. 
  * The state and/or country from which you are connecting directly to our site. 
  * The Search Engine you used to connect directly to our site. 

The above information is used by software programs on our website to create summary statistics which allow us to assess the number of visitors to the different sections of our site, identify what information is of most and least interest, determine technical design specifications, monitor system performance, and help us make our site more useful to visitors. 

_If you identify yourself by sending an E-mail containing personal information:_  
You also may decide to send us personally identifying information, for example your mailing address, in an electronic mail message requesting that information be mailed to you. Information collected in this manner is used solely for responding to requests for information. We may forward your E-mail to other Spreety employees who are better able to respond to you. 

_If you link to other sites outside the Spreety Website:_  
Our Website has many links to other sites. When you link to any of these sites, you are no longer on our site and are subject to the privacy policy of the new site. 

_Cookie Use Notice:_   
The Spreety Website employs "cookies" to provide better service to its customers. Spreety does not use cookies to collect any personally identifying information from users or to track user activities beyond our web site. Spreety does not maintain copies of cookies on our servers after you leave our web site. Cookies are small pieces of data that are exchanged between a web site and a user's computer which enable a "session", or "dialog", to be established between the two machines. With the session established, Spreety is able to tailor its responses (i.e., identify and provide you with the information you want) and help you traverse our web pages in the most efficient and effective manner possible. The session is often broken when Spreety does not receive further requests from your computer or you simply exit your browser. Spreety does not use "session cookies", which are types of cookies that are temporarily stored in your computer's memory. Session cookies are normally deleted from a user's computer when the user logs off the computer or the user exits the browser. Spreety does issue "persistent cookies", types of cookies that could be stored permanently on your workstation and reused each time you visit the Spreety web site. Those cookies may be stored on some user's computers and, in some cases, may be updated by the user's browser when revisiting the Spreety web site. In the event a cookie is found on your workstation, which was issued from a Spreety web site, you may remove it without adversely affecting your future visits to our web site. 

For security purposes and to ensure that this service remains available to all users, our website also employs software programs to monitor network traffic to identify unauthorized attempts to upload or change information, or otherwise cause damage. Unauthorized attempts to upload information or change information on this service are strictly prohibited and may be punishable under the Computer Fraud and Abuse Act of 1986 and the National Information Infrastructure Protection Act of 1996. 

**Disclaimer Statement**

Spreety maintains this web site to enhance public access to Spreety information. This is a service that is continually under development. While we try to keep the information timely and accurate, we make no guarantees. We will make an effort to correct errors brought to our attention. 

The documents on this server contain hypertext pointers to information created and maintained by other public and private organizations. Please be aware that we do not control or guarantee the accuracy, relevance, timeliness, or completeness of this outside information. Further, the inclusion of pointers to particular items in hypertext is not intended to reflect their importance, nor is it intended to endorse any views expressed or products or services offered by the author of the reference or the organization operating the server on which the reference is maintained.
